(NARRATOR READING)
(OAR ENGINE STARTING)
OPERATOR ON PHONE:
911, what's your
emergency?
(BOY GASPING)
911, what's your
emergency?
Are you there?
(ORYING) There...
There are
people here.
Okay, calm down.
Where are you?
What's your address?
L don't know.
Are you in danger?
Yes. Yes.
What's your name?
Jordan.
We need help.
Okay. Oan you tell me
what street you're on?
L don't know
where we are.
Jordan, who
are you with?
We went into
the house.
We found people.
You found who, Jordan?
Who did you find?
There's blood
on the walls.
Help us! Help us!
Jordan. Jordan, calm down.
It's everywhere.
Jordan, what happened?
There's blood
everywhere.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(DOOR OPENING)
(MELLOW MUSIO PLAYING)
When did you do all this?
Today. With Mike.
When you were with
the girls. L thought
you'd like it.
You can have
this room. L'm gonna
get set up out there.
(JAMES SIGHS)
Yeah, l don't know
about the tub.
Didn't know
ifthe roses go
in first or after.
Yeah, l don't
know either.
(CHUCKLES)
Here.
Let me.
Thank you.
Okay.
Mike, it's me.
We're at the
house now.
I... l know you're
fucking drunk, maybe
you're asleep now, but...
(WATER SPLASHING)
Uh...
JAMES: L'll tell you when
l see you, but things...
They didn'twork out
the way l planned at all.
Um...
l'm going to need
you to come out
here and get me.
Justwheneveryou wake
up in the morning. L'm
going to give herthe car.
Just call me when
you get this, okay?
L know it's a bitch
to come all the way
out here
but, sorry,
this sucks. Okay.
Hi.
Come outside
with me.
L onlywanted
to dance with you.
We're dancing
right now.
Jerk.
You're ajerk.
Oh, it's freezing.
Let's get in the car.
Wait a second.
What?
L justwant to
tell you something.
What do you
wanna tell me?
L rememberthe first
time l ever saw you.
(CLOCK CHIMING)
Lt's really nice,
everything you did.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Here.
L can't keep it.
L can't take it back.
Please.
Just take it, please.
(CORK POPPING)
Here.
(BLOWING SOFTLY)
Your clothes are
in the bedroom,
ifyou want.
L wanna wearthis.
You know, l only
get to wear it tonight.
It makes me feel pretty.
You are pretty.
L'm so sorry it
wasn't the way you
thought itwould be.
L'm really sorry.
Well, what do we do now?
L don't know.
(SIGHS)
L'm just not
ready yet.
Okay.
James, please...
Please.
Talk to me.
Christ.
This is embarrassing.
(MELLOW OOUNTRY MUSIO PLAYING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
You are my girl.
(GASPS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
What is it, like,
4:00 in the morning?
(CONTINUES KNOCKING)
Hi.
Hello.
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKING)
Ls Tamara here?
No. No, you got
the wrong house.
You sure?
Yeah. L'm sorry.
See you later.
Thatwas weird.
Yeah.
You know, people
get lost out here.
Should l go get her?
KRISTEN: She seemed okay.
L mean, l think she
would've said if she wasn't.
KRISTEN: (WHISPERING)
Lt's cold out there.
L'm out of cigarettes.
L'll go get
you some more.
L didn't mean that.
You don't have to.
L'll just go to sleep.
L'm tired, anyway.
No, you won't.
L'll try.
It's all right,
l want to drive
for a while, anyway.
Let me light
you a fire.
L was thinking when
you were taking a bath.
L wantyou to take
the car back tomorrow.
What do you mean?
L don't think a
road trip's a good
idea right now.
L called Mike.
He's gonna come out
and get me in the morning.
Are you sure
that's whatyou want?
(BLOWING)
Yeah.
Okay, l'll be back.
Lfyou want, we
can talk some more.
We don't have
to. Okay?
You gonna be
okay here?
Yeah, l'll be fine.
Okay.
Thanks for lighting
me a fire.
Sure.
(MELLOW MUSIO PLAYING)
(PLAYING PIANO)
(BANG ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING)
Hello?
WOMAN: Ls
Tamara home?
You already
came by here.
Are you sure?
(FOOTSTEPS FADING)
(CHIMES RINGING)
(CLATTERING)
(COUGHS)
(BEEPING)
(BANG ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Oh, come on.
(BEEPS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
James, where are you?
That girl came back.
That girl, l mean,
she keeps knocking
on the door.
What do you mean?
L heard her voice.
No, l didn't
open the door.
L don't know.
The battery is dead.
L'm charging it right now.
Okay, okay.
L justwantyou
to come home, okay?
No, l'm fine,
butjust, you
know, hurry.
How far away are you?
Okay.
Will you just stay
on the phone with me?
(BEEPING)
James?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BANG ON DOOR)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RUMBLING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(WHISPERING)
This isn't happening.
(METAL CLANKING)
(METALLIC GRATING)
(SCREAMING)
(REOORD REPEATING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(THUDDING)
(CLATTERING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(SCREAMS) Go away!
(RECORD STOPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Jamie.
Kristen.
There is
someone
out there.
What are you doing? What?
There's something...
They'll hearyou.
Stop, stop, stop.
Shh!
What happened
to your hand?
(KRISTEN SOBBING)
Stop. Stop!
Come here, come here.
Sit down. Sit down,
sit down, sit down.
How do you know
there's somebody
out there?
L saw a man
at the back door.
He's wearing a mask.
What do you mean?
Like a ski mask? What?
L don't know.
A fucking mask!
Okay, okay. Calm down.
Jamie, l'm so scared.
Okay.
Don't go out there.
Please, don't go.
Please, stop.
Just stay here.
L'm right here. Stop.
No one out here.
Nobody. Come here.
(SOBBING)
Come here.
It's okay,
there's
nothing here.
So, what do
you wanna do?
L don't know.
Kristen?
Kristen,
what is it?
She's watching us.
JAMES: She looks
like a ghost.
You want me
to go talk to her?
They don'twanna talk.
Well, theywant something.
Peoplejust don't
stand out there
staring at us like that.
Theywant something.
Shit.
What?
L left my phone
in the car, l'm
gonna go get it.
You can't go out there.
Why?
One ofthem
came in here
and took my phone.
Kristen, nobody
came in here.
KRISTEN: She's gone.
Fuck!
Shit!
(EXCLAIMS)
(BANGING)
(DOG YELPING)
What do you want?
All right, get the
fuck out of here!
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(SOFTLY) James!
Kristen, go back inside.
What's happening?
Kristen...
(BANGING)
Kristen, go.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CREAKING)
Jesus Christ,
what are you doing?
L'm sorry.
L'm waiting
foryou.
L wantyou
to getyourthings.
Putyour shoes on.
Did you find your phone?
No, l told you,
they took my phone.
Babe, l put it
in your bag.
James, it's not
in the bag.
L plugged it into
the wall, and when
l came back itwas gone.
It'sjust, l don't
understand. We checked
the whole house,
and nobody in here.
Let me see your hand.
What are you
thinking?
Since we've been
here l haven't heard
a dog bark,
a car pass, nothing.
Just us and them.
Why are they
doing this?
Kristen, l don'twantyou
to think about that, okay?
Don't think about it.
Doesn't matter right now.
We don't need a reason
ifthey come through
that door.
Okay?
What is it?
Lt's my phone.
We gotta get
out of here.
Shit.
KRISTEN: Who is that?
JAMES: L don't know.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Get out
ofthe car.
(KRISTEN SCREAMING)
Come on.
(CAR HONKING)
(EXHALES)
James, we
need a gun.
L'm looking.
Does your dad
have a gun?
Kristen,
l'm looking.
There was one
here when l was a kid.
He always hid it.
Let's go to
the bedroom.
KRISTEN: Oh, my God!
(BANGING)
KRISTEN: What
are you doing?
Looking for bullets.
Stop. L got them,
l got them.
L don't know how
to use this thing.
What do you mean?
L'm not sure l even
know how to load it.
Butyou said
you used to hunt
with your dad.
No, l never did.
Itwasjust something
that l said.
When l open the
door, l justwant
you to run, okay?
(SCREAMING)
Block the door,
block the door.
(KRISTEN SCREAMING)
Push!
Come on.
We're not gonna
fucking die here.
We're gonna sit here, we're
gonna wait forthe fucking
cops to come, orwhatever,
butwe're not
gonna fucking die.
(RUMBLING)
(UPBEAT OOUNTRY MUSIO PLAYING
ON GRAMOPHONE)
Yo, Jimmy James.
What's up, buddy?
Lt's Mike. Listen,
man, l'm outside.
L got here early.
L just decided
to come out,
and you know,
just be here
foryou as soon
as l possibly could,
because you know how
l like to wait on you
hand and fucking foot.
(EXCLAIMS)
What the fuck?
(CHIMES RINGING)
(OOUNTRY MUSIO PLAYING)
Hello?
Jimmy?
Kristen?
Hello?
Kristen, l shot him.
He didn't have a mask.
What?
Why didn't he have
a fucking mask?
What do you mean,
he didn't have a mask?
James?
(GASPS)
What?
Oh, God!
What is it?
(CRYING) Stay there.
James, answer me.
Oh, fuck!
What?
Don't. Stay there.
Get off of me.
Stop it.
It's Mike. Mike.
Please don't look.
It's Mike.
(SOBBING) Oh, God.
Baby, it's
notyourfault.
He was my best friend.
He's my best friend.
What am l gonna do?
(KRISTEN COUGHING)
KRISTEN: Where
are you going?
L'm gonna go
outside. L wantyou
to hide somewhere.
What are you
talking about?
There's an old radio
at the barn, l'm gonna
try and call for help.
L don't know
what else to do.
It's okay, l'm gonna
come right back foryou.
Listen, l wantyou
to go, and l wantyou
to hide there.
L'll keep them away.
L'll come find you.
James, no. L want
to come with you.
Kristen, please, it'll
be okay, l promise.
L'll be fine.
(WHISPERING)
Be careful. James.
Oh, shit!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GUNSHOT FIRED)
James?
Ah!
(CRYING IN PAIN)
Oh, fuck!
(THUDDING)
(CLATTERING)
James?
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(MAN OHATTERING ON RADIO)
Hello?
(CRYING) Can anybody hear me?
(VOICE APPROACHING)
(CLATTERING)
(THUDDING)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
(THUDDING)
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(BANGING)
MAN ON RADIO: This is K-50.
Hello?
Can you
hear me?
Hello?
Please,
answer me.
(MAN OHATTERING ON RADIO)
Help me.
Where are you?
(SCREAMING)
(METAL CLATTERING)
(PIANO PLAYING)
(CLATTERING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
He's gonna
kill you.
Why are you
doing this
to us?
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(CHOKING)
James!
You're gonna die.
JAMES: Kristen, run!
(SCREAMING)
Let me out!
JAMES: Kristen! Run!
Jamie!
(SCREAMING)
(MAN BREATHING DEEPLY)
(KRISTEN SCREAMING)
(KRISTEN SOBBING)
Why are you
doing this to us?
Because you
were home.
L love you.
Baby!
No! Please! No!
No! Please!
You don't
have to do
this. Please!
You can stop now.
You... Please! No!
Please,
listen to me.
Please.
You can stop
now. You don't
have to do this.
KRISTEN: (SCREAMING) No!
KRISTEN: Baby,
look at me.
Look at my face.
Don't look,
please.
(EXCLAIMS)
Please! Please!
Please, don't!
No!
KRISTEN: No!
(KRISTEN SOBBING)
(KRISTEN ExOLAIMS IN PAIN)
WOMAN: Can l have one?
Are you a sinner?
Sometimes.
WOMAN: Lt'll be
easier next time.
(SCREAMING)